<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rust Lang - Compiler Team</title>
    <link>/docs/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Rust Lang - Compiler Team</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/docs/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/about/chat-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/about/chat-platform/</guid>
      <description>The compiler team hangs out primarily in the rust-lang Zulip these days. The #t-compiler/help stream is a great place to ask questions. In addition, each working group has 1 or more streams where they communicate.
You can also find us on the rust-lang Discord, in the #compiler channel.
The #rustc IRC channel on irc.mozilla.org is in a &amp;ldquo;quasi-deprecated&amp;rdquo; status and is not recommended.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/about/steering-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/about/steering-meeting/</guid>
      <description>Steering Meeting The compiler steering meeting is the place for high-level discussion and planning. The meeting takes place weekly. The topics of the meeting are selected at periodic planning meetings. See the steering meeting procedure for more details. See #58850 for more information.
See the compiler team calendar for the topics of the next scheduled meetings. There is also a dedicated internals thread.
The steering meeting takes place on Zulip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/docs/about/triage-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/about/triage-meeting/</guid>
      <description>Triage Meeting The compiler triage meeting is the place for tracking regressions, progress on urgent bugs and checking-in with the compiler team&amp;rsquo;s working groups. Each meeting, two working groups (rotating) check-in with their progress and blockers.
The meeting takes place every week. See the compiler team calendar for the next scheduled meeting (normally weekly).
The triage meeting takes place on Zulip. Look for a topic like &amp;ldquo;#54818 weekly meeting YYYY-MM-DD&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;weekly meeting YYYY-MM-DD&amp;rdquo; (with the proper date, of course).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>