<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Compiler team on Rust Lang - Compiler Team</title><link>https://rust-lang.github.io/compiler-team/about/</link><description>Recent content in Compiler team on Rust Lang - Compiler Team</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://rust-lang.github.io/compiler-team/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chat platform</title><link>https://rust-lang.github.io/compiler-team/about/chat-platform/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rust-lang.github.io/compiler-team/about/chat-platform/</guid><description>The compiler team hangs out in the rust-lang Zulip these days. Feel free to introduce yourself and say hi in the #new-members stream! The #t-compiler/help stream is also a great place to ask questions. In addition, each working group has one or more streams where they communicate.</description></item><item><title>Code Of Conduct</title><link>https://rust-lang.github.io/compiler-team/about/CODE_OF_CONDUCT/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rust-lang.github.io/compiler-team/about/CODE_OF_CONDUCT/</guid><description>The Rust Code of Conduct A version of this document can be found online.
Conduct Contact: rust-mods@rust-lang.org
We are committed to providing a friendly, safe and welcoming environment for all, regardless of level of experience, gender identity and expression, sexual orientation, disability, personal appearance, body size, race, ethnicity, age, religion, nationality, or other similar characteristic. On IRC, please avoid using overtly sexual nicknames or other nicknames that might detract from a friendly, safe and welcoming environment for all.</description></item><item><title>Steering meeting</title><link>https://rust-lang.github.io/compiler-team/about/steering-meeting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rust-lang.github.io/compiler-team/about/steering-meeting/</guid><description>Steering Meeting The compiler steering meeting is the place for high-level discussion and planning. The meeting takes place weekly. The topics of the meeting are selected at periodic planning meetings. See the steering meeting procedure for more details. See #58850 for more information.
See the compiler team calendar for the topics of the next scheduled meetings. There is also a dedicated internals thread.
The steering meeting takes place on Zulip.</description></item><item><title>Triage Meeting</title><link>https://rust-lang.github.io/compiler-team/about/triage-meeting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rust-lang.github.io/compiler-team/about/triage-meeting/</guid><description>Triage Meeting The compiler triage meeting is the place for tracking regressions, progress on urgent bugs and checking-in with the compiler team&amp;rsquo;s working groups. Each meeting, two working groups (rotating) check-in with their progress and blockers.
The meeting takes place every week. See the compiler team calendar for the next scheduled meeting (normally weekly).
The triage meeting takes place on Zulip. Look for a topic like &amp;ldquo;#54818 weekly meeting YYYY-MM-DD&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;weekly meeting YYYY-MM-DD&amp;rdquo; (with the proper date, of course).</description></item></channel></rss>